<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--BionicInternalSupport-->
  <BionicInternalSupport.label>bionic internal support</BionicInternalSupport.label>
  <BionicInternalSupport.description>An advanced artificial internal support. Useful replacement to have on hand for when an internal component of a bionic prosthesis breaks.</BionicInternalSupport.description>
  <!--BionicArm-->
  <BionicArm.label>bionic arm</BionicArm.label>
  <BionicArm.description>An advanced artificial arm. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological arm in almost every way.</BionicArm.description>
  <!--BionicForearm-->
  <BionicForearm.label>bionic forearm</BionicForearm.label>
  <BionicForearm.description>An advanced artificial forearm. Silenced mini-servos give great strength, while the biogel nerve-link gives exquisite control. A lattice-dust healing system allows it to recover from damage. It is better than a biological arm in almost every way.</BionicForearm.description>
  <!--BionicHand-->
  <BionicHand.label>bionic hand</BionicHand.label>
  <BionicHand.description>An advanced artificial hand. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological hand in almost every way.</BionicHand.description>
  <!--BionicFinger-->
  <BionicFinger.label>bionic finger</BionicFinger.label>
  <BionicFinger.description>An advanced artificial finger. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological finger in almost every way.</BionicFinger.description>
  <!--BionicLeg-->
  <BionicLeg.label>bionic leg</BionicLeg.label>
  <BionicLeg.description>An advanced artificial leg. With its biogel nerve-link, powerful mini-servos, and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological leg in almost every way.</BionicLeg.description>
  <!--BionicFoot-->
  <BionicFoot.label>bionic foot</BionicFoot.label>
  <BionicFoot.description>An advanced artificial foot. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological foot in almost every way.</BionicFoot.description>
  <!--BionicToe-->
  <BionicToe.label>bionic toe</BionicToe.label>
  <BionicToe.description>An advanced artificial toe. With its biogel nerve-link and lattice-dust healing system, it is better than a biological toe in almost every way.</BionicToe.description>
</LanguageData>