<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--ArchotechInternalSupport-->
  <ArchotechInternalSupport.label>archotech internal support</ArchotechInternalSupport.label>
  <ArchotechInternalSupport.description>An artificial internal support built by an archotech. Useful replacement to have on hand for when an internal component of an archotech prosthesis breaks.</ArchotechInternalSupport.description>
  <!--ArchotechArm-->
  <ArchotechArm.label>archotech arm</ArchotechArm.label>
  <ArchotechArm.description>An artifical arm built by an archotech. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechArm.description>
  <!--ArchotechForearm-->
  <ArchotechForearm.label>archotech forearm</ArchotechForearm.label>
  <ArchotechForearm.description>An artifical forearm built by an archotech. It's strong enough to crush a thick hardwood branch in its hand, and precise enough to write a sonnet on a grain of rice. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechForearm.description>
  <!--ArchotechHand-->
  <ArchotechHand.label>archotech hand</ArchotechHand.label>
  <ArchotechHand.description>An artifical hand built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural hand, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Requires archotech surgery research to install it.</ArchotechHand.description>
  <!--ArchotechFinger-->
  <ArchotechFinger.label>archotech finger</ArchotechFinger.label>
  <ArchotechFinger.description>An artifical finger built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural finger, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Requires archotech surgery research to install it.</ArchotechFinger.description>
  <!--ArchotechLeg-->
  <ArchotechLeg.label>archotech leg</ArchotechLeg.label>
  <ArchotechLeg.description>An artifical leg built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural flesh, but a pair of these can move the user as fast as a decent car, and it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Its internal workings are a mystery to all human minds.</ArchotechLeg.description>
  <!--ArchotechFoot-->
  <ArchotechFoot.label>archotech foot</ArchotechFoot.label>
  <ArchotechFoot.description>An artifical foot built by an archotech. It looks and feels like natural foot, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Requires archotech surgery research to install it.</ArchotechFoot.description>
  <!--ArchotechToe-->
  <ArchotechToe.label>archotech toe</ArchotechToe.label>
  <ArchotechToe.description>An artifical toe built by an archotech. It looks and feels like a natural toe, but it's harder to damage than plasteel. Even if it is harmed, it repairs itself over time. Requires archotech surgery research to install it.</ArchotechToe.description>
</LanguageData>