<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<LanguageData>
  <!--SimpleProstheticArm-->
  <SimpleProstheticArm.label>prosthetic arm</SimpleProstheticArm.label>
  <SimpleProstheticArm.description>An arm prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real arm.</SimpleProstheticArm.description>
  <!--SimpleProstheticHand-->
  <SimpleProstheticHand.label>prosthetic hand</SimpleProstheticHand.label>
  <SimpleProstheticHand.description>A hand prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real hand.</SimpleProstheticHand.description>
  <!--SimpleProstheticFinger-->
  <SimpleProstheticFinger.label>prosthetic finger</SimpleProstheticFinger.label>
  <SimpleProstheticFinger.description>A finger prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real finger.</SimpleProstheticFinger.description>
  <!--SimpleProstheticLeg-->
  <SimpleProstheticLeg.label>prosthetic leg</SimpleProstheticLeg.label>
  <SimpleProstheticLeg.description>A leg prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real leg.</SimpleProstheticLeg.description>
  <!--SimpleProstheticFoot-->
  <SimpleProstheticFoot.label>prosthetic foot</SimpleProstheticFoot.label>
  <SimpleProstheticFoot.description>A foot prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real foot.</SimpleProstheticFoot.description>
  <!--SimpleProstheticToe-->
  <SimpleProstheticToe.label>prosthetic toe</SimpleProstheticToe.label>
  <SimpleProstheticToe.description>A toe prosthesis. While it lacks a neural interface, its complex arrangement of internal joints allows it to mimic natural movement quite convincingly. Still, it is inferior to a real toe.</SimpleProstheticToe.description>
</LanguageData>